[{"answer": "Take toilet paper for example. Do you realize that toilet paper has not changed in my lifetime? It's just paper on a cardboard roll, that's it. And in ten thousand years, it will still be exactly the same because really, what else can they do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "And everything else has changed. But toilet paper is exactly the same, and will be so until we're dead", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I can't stand him, he is so pretentious", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No, my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Something's up, there's something in the air", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Well, I think this is it", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What's it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah, he's dating a crayon", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Toilet paper", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Softer", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What is that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You painted your face", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yup", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Huge matzoh ball", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well, I still think it's wrong", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I'm not taking anyone's side", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Oh, my friend, what are you waiting for", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Oh, no no no, you gotta call him the next day, it's common courtesy", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Who died", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "So he actually had it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "So, so what do you want me to do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yeah, well he started it", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Girlfriend, yeah, right", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Nothing doing. my friend, I didn't do anything. It's the monkey that should be apologizing to me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Well, I'm sorry. Well, my friend, I tried to put the good word in for you with that place, but I don't think she heard me. You know, left ear", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Well, not exactly", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I don't know if he's mad", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yeah, that's right", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Well, alright, so you don't like the face painting, I just won't paint it anymore", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, it's not that I don't like you, but, well to be perfectly honest, I'm just having some trouble getting past the face painting", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Yeah, but you like the face painting", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Well, I'm going to the game tonight, and me and these five other guys are gonna take our shirts off and spell out 'Devils'", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No, I said no more face painting, and as you can see this is not my face", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, my friend, the reason I called is I just wanted to thank you for the tickets from the other night", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Face-Painter.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Oh, you already gave them away", "qsentId": 38}]